On Halloween, finding the right costume can be murder
The Body is a thriller, tv movie, horror film directed by Paul Davis.
In Los Angeles, on Halloween night, a hitman tries to transport a corpse in plain sight, but people he stumbles upon on the street,
believing that his sophisticated appearance is a magnificent disguise, constantly stand in his way to congratulate him.
Wilkes, played by Tom Bateman.
Maggie, played by Rebecca Rittenhouse.
Dorothy, played by Aurora Perrineau.
Alan, played by David Hull.
Jack, played by Ray Santiago.
Nick, played by Harvey Guillén.
Our Body (Korean: 아워 바디; RR: Awo badi) is a 2018 South Korean
drama film written and directed by Han Ka-ram.
It is her debut feature film.
The film explores themes of hitman, holiday,
halloween, halloween party, serial killer.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.